Guide to the Records and Papers of Terry Sanford, 1945-1998 UA.03.60.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Series 1. Duke University. President Terry Sanford Records, 1969-1985.
  - Subseries 1.1. Subject files, 1969-1985, 175 ln. ft. (about 150,000 items
    - Buildings. Music Building, 1967-1980 (Box 26)
    - Buildings. Naming of, [1970-1983] (Box 26)
    - Buildings. Nanaline H. Duke, Dedication [1968] (Box 26)
    - Buildings. Perkins Library, Dedication [1970] (Box 26)
    - Buildings. Swimming Pool [1969] (Box 26)
    - Bureau of Public Information (Bill Green). 1970- (Box 26)
    - Burns, Captain Otway, Desk of (Box 26)
    - Bus Service. [1974] (Box 26)
    - Business Executives Symposium. 1978, 1984 (Box 26)
    - Business Office. Accounting. [1975-1984] (Box 26)
    - Business Office. Benefits and Records. [1970-1984] (Box 26)
    - Business Office. Bursar's Office. [1982-1985] (Box 26)
    - Business Office. Business Manager (R. James Henderson) [1976-1985] (Box 26)
    - Business Office. Controller (John Adcock) [1984] (Box 26)
    - Business Office. Fuller, Peyton [1971-1985] (Box 26)
    - Business Office. Henricksen, C.G., Vice-president and Treasurer. 1970-1971. (Box 26)
    - Business Office. Huestis, C.B. 1982-1985 (Box 26)
    - Business Office. Huestis, C.B. [1977-1981] (Box 26)
    - Business Office. Huestis, C.B. [ca. 1974-1976] (Box 26)
    - Business Office. Married student housing [1970] (Box 26)
    - Business Office. Physical Plant Services. [1974-1979] (Box 26)
    - Business Office. Treasurer. S.C. Harward. 1963-1985 (Box 26)
    - Business-Higher Education Forum. [1982-1985] (Box 26)
    - Byers, Ralph. [1976-1977] (Box 26)
    - C. General correspondence, 1970-1985, 15 folders (Box 27)
    - Calendar, [University, 1970-1985] (Box 28)
    - Campus publications [1971] (Box 28)
    - Canada. Prime Minister Pierre Trudeau [1974] (Box 28)
    - Canadian Studies Center [1981-1985] (Box 28)
    - Cannon, Charles A., and family (Box 28)
    - Carnegie Commission on Higher Education [1973-1983] (Box 28)
    - Carnegie Corporation (Box 28)
    - Carnegie Council on Policy Studies in Higher Education. 1978 (Box 28)
    - Carolina Repertory Company. [1971-1972] (Box 28)
    - Carter, Everett A. (Box 28)
    - Carter, Jimmy. President (Box 28)
    - Carver, Roy J. (Box 28)
    - Center for Administrative Justice [American Bar Association] (Box 28)
    - Center for Commonwealth Studies, 1969-1978 (Box 28)
    - Center for Creative Leadership, [1970-1975] (Box 28)
    - Center for Creative Leadership, [1976-1985] (Box 29)
    - Center for Democratic Policy, 1981 (Box 29)
    - Center for Educational Policy, [1978-1980] (Box 29)
    - Center for Lifetime Learning (Box 29)
    - Center for National Policy, 1982-1986 (Box 29)
    - Center for Research in College Instruction of Science and Math (Box 30)
    - Center for Research on Public Interest Investment Issues, 1972-1973 (Box 30)
    - Center for Southern Studies (Box 30)
    - Center for the Study of Aging and Human Development (Box 30)
    - Center for the Study of Federalism (Box 30)
    - Center for the Study of the Governorship and State Policymaking, [1981-1982] (Box 30)
    - Central Campus Housing (Box 30)
    - Chadwick, William. Paintings (Box 30)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Greater Durham (Box 30)
    - Chancellor. A. Kenneth Pye, 1970-1971 (Box 30)
    - Chancellor. A. Kenneth Pye, 1976-1982 (Box 30)
    - Chancellor. H. Keith H. Brodie, 1982-1985 (Box 30)
    - Chancellor. John O. Blackburn, 1971-1976 (Box 30)
    - Change magazine articles, 1971-1980. (Box 30)
    - Chapel. Chapel Committee, [1971-1985] (Box 30)
    - Chapel. Chapel organs (Box 31)
    - Chapel. Chapel service for government officials (Box 31)
    - Chapel. Crypt (Box 31)
    - Chapel. Fiftieth Anniversary Commemoration of the Laying of the Cornerstone (Box 31)
    - Chapel. Sermons (Box 31)
    - Chaplain, 1970-1972 (Box 31)
    - Charlesworth, James H., Dr. (Box 31)
    - Charlotte Resource Council (Box 31)
    - Child Care Center for Duke Employees (Box 31)
    - Children's Home Society of North Carolina (Box 31)
    - Children, Disadvantaged, National Advisory Council on the Education of (Box 31)
    - Children, Duke School for. 1982-1984. Preschool and Primary Program. (Box 31)
    - Children with mental disabilities (Box 31)
      Scope and Contents
      The title of this folder has been changed along with the removal of the name for the National Association for Retarded Children due to the use of no longer accepted terms to refer to children with mental disabilities. Note that materials in this folder may contain such outdated language.
    - China, 1975 (Box 31)
    - China, [c. 1977-1980] (Box 31)
    - China. China Encounter. (publication) [1976-1977] (Box 31)
    - China. All-China Youth Federation, [1983-1984] (Box 31)
    - China. China Exchange, [c. 1971-1980] (Box 31)
    - China. Hatem, George, Dr., [1978-1985] (Box 31)
    - China. Jospeh B. Kennedy's Program (Box 31)
    - China. People's Republic. Trip diary, 1980: A Fast Stroll Through the Edges of China, April 23 - May 8, 1980 / by Terry Sanford (Box 31)
    - China. Duke delegation to, 1971-1975 (Box 32)
    - Chowan College (Box 32)
    - Christ School (Arden, NC) (Box 32)
    - Christian Scientists, Duke policy on (Box 32)
    - Christmas cards (Box 32)
    - Christmas thank-you notes (Box 32)
    - Chronicle of Higher Education (Box 32)
    - Chronicle, [Duke University] (Box 32)
    - Citizens for Court Modernization (Box 32)
    - Citizens for a New Prosperity (Box 32)
    - Citizens' Committee for Government Reorganization (Box 32)
    - Citizens' Conference on State Legislatures: see LEGIS 50 (Box 32)
    - Clark, Heman and Bayard (Box 32)
    - Cleland Fund (Box 32)
    - Cleland, James T., Dr. (Box 32)
    - Clodfelter, Danny (Box 32)
    - Coalition for Human Needs and Budget Priorities (Box 32)
    - Coalition for Rural America (Box 32)
    - Coastal Plains Institute (Box 32)
    - Cole, R. Taylor (Box 32)
    - College Entrance Examination Board (Box 32)
    - College Military Deferments, 1971 (Box 32)
    - Commencement, 1970-1980, 11 folders (Box 33)
    - Commencement Marshals, [1970-1973] (Box 34)
    - Commencement, 1981-1984, 4 folders (Box 34)
    - Commencement. Chris Mimm's file on procedure (Box 34)
    - Committee. Academic Council Committee to Study the Nature and Role of the Academic Council (Christie Committee), 1972 (Box 34)
    - Committee. Art and History Preservation (Box 34)
    - Committee. Audio-visual Program (Jay Rutherford) (Box 34)
    - Committee. Black Affairs, President's Council on, 1975-1983 (Box 34)
    - Committee. Campus Community Council (Box 34)
    - Committee. Capital Gifts, 1977- (Box 34)
    - Committee. Chancellor. Chancellor's Advisory Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 34)
    - Committee. Communications. Video Task Force (Box 34)
    - Committee. Conflict Resolution (ad hoc), 1971 (Box 34)
    - Committee. Contraception and Abortion (Box 34)
    - Committee. Corporate Support of Private Universities (Box 34)
    - Committee. Committee on Committees (Box 35)
    - Committee. Curriculum Committee (Box 35)
    - Committee. Duke University Employee Relations Advisory Committee (DUERAC) (Box 35)
    - Committee. Economic Development [1978-1984] (Box 35)
    - Committee. Education Programs, Full Funding of (Box 35)
    - Committee. Education, Commission on the Uses of Technology (Box 35)
    - Committee. Educational Facilities (Box 35)
    - Committee. Educational Policy Program in Trinity College (Box 35)
    - Committee. Environmental Concerns (Box 35)
    - Committee. Epoch Campaign (Box 35)
    - Committee. Faculty Fringe Benefits (Box 35)
    - Committee. Federal Relations (Box 35)
    - Committee. Forest, [Duke] (Box 35)
    - Committee. Golf Course Policy (Box 35)
    - Committee. Graduate Faculty (Box 35)
    - Committee. Hunger, Presidential Commission on (Box 35)
    - Committee. On Inter-University Center for Inter-Professional Education (Box 35)
    - Committee. Personnel Policy (Box 35)
    - Committee. Publications Board (Box 35)
    - Committee. Residential Life (Box 35)
    - Committee. Search. Admissions Director (Box 35)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      NOTE:Search Committee files are RESTRICTED
    - Committee. Search. Advisory (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Alumni Affairs Director, 1982 (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Business School Dean (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Chancellor and Provost Committee, 1970 (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Chancellor, 1976 (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Chancellor, 1982 (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Chaplain (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Data Processing, Vice-Chancellor for, 1982-1982 (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Development Officer (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Divinity School Dean, 1970-1982 (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Engineering (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Graduate School, Dean, 1979-1980 (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Law School Dean, 1970, 1973, 1977 (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Minister to the University, 1983-1984 (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. President of the University (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Provost, 1971 (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Provost, 1978 (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Provost, 1982-1983 (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Vice-President for Business, Finance, andLaw. (Box 36)
    - Committee. Search. Psychology Department Chairman (Box 37)
    - Committee. Search. Trinity College of Arts and Sciences, Dean (Box 37)
    - Committee. Search. University Counsel (Box 37)
    - Committee. Search. University Librarian (Box 37)
    - Committee. Social Implications of Investment Policies (Box 37)
    - Committee. Sponsored Research (Box 37)
    - Committee. Student Union (Box 37)
    - Committee. Study Abroad (Box 37)
    - Committee. Traffic Commission (Box 37)
    - Committee. Traffic Commission Hearing Panel (Box 37)
    - Committee. Trustee. Academic Affairs (Box 37)
      NOTE:Trustee Committee files are RESTRICTED
    - Committee. Trustee. Art Museum (Box 37)
    - Committee. Trustee. Buildings and Grounds (Box 37)
    - Committee. Trustee. Business and Finance (Box 37)
    - Committee. Trustee. Institutional Advancement (Box 37)
    - Committee. Trustee. Investments, 1972-1977 (Box 37)
    - Committee. Trustee. Investments, 1978 (Box 37)
    - Committee. Trustee. Investments, 1979 (Box 37)
    - Committee. Trustee. Investments, 1980 (Box 37)
    - Committee. Trustee. Investments, University Investment Committee, 1978 (Box 37)
    - Committee. Trustee. Trustee-Faculty, on Honorary Degrees, 1958-1980 (Box 37)
    - Committee. Trustee. Investments, 1981 (Box 38)
    - Committee. Trustee. Investments, 1982 (Box 38)
    - Committee. Trustee. Investments, 1983 (Box 38)
    - Committee. Trustee. Investments, 1984 (Box 38)
    - Committee. Trustee. Investments, 1985 (Box 38)
    - Committee. Trustee. Medical Center Affairs (Box 38)
    - Committee. Trustee. Miscellaneous [rosters] (Box 38)
    - Committee. Trustee. Nominations, 1970-1985, 4 folders (Box 38)
    - Committee. Trustee. Student Affairs (Box 38)
    - Committee. Trustee. Student Appointees (Box 38)
    - Committee. Trustee. Watson Report, 1969 (Report of the Special Committee on Functions and Organization of the Board of Trustees) (Box 38)
    - Committee. Undergraduate Faculty Council of Arts and Sciences (Box 38)
    - Committee. University Budget Committee (Box 38)
    - Committee. University Center Advisory Committee (Box 38)
    - Committee. University Planning (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Executive Committee (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Sub-committee on Admissions and Financial Aid (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Sub-committee on Athletics and Physical Education (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Sub-committee on Faculty Development (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Sub-committee on Graduate Academic Programs (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Sub-committee on International Programs (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Sub-committee on Libraries (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Sub-committee on Medical Center and Health Affairs (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Sub-committee on Non-curricular Life at Duke (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Sub-committee on Physical Facilities (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Sub-committee on Professional Schools (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Sub-committee on Regionaland State Responsibilities (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Sub-committee on the Fine Arts (Box 39)
    - Committee. University Planning. Sub-committee on Undergraduate Academic Programs (Box 39)
    - Committees. Administrative and Faculty Committees in the Arts and Sciences / by Steve Johnston, 1970 (Box 39)
    - Committees. Committees at Duke University. [Office ofInstitutional Studies, 1963] (Box 39)
    - Committees. Student appointees (Box 39)
    - Common Cause. (John W. Gardner, Chairman) (Box 39)
    - Commonwealth Fund (Box 39)
    - Community Radio Workshops, Inc. (Spruill, R.E.), 1971-1972 (Box 39)
    - Community Relations [Office of] (Box 39)
    - Compact for Education (Box 39)
    - Complaints (Box 39)
    - Conference Board, The. [New York, NY], 1970-1978, 1985 (Box 39)
    - Conference Board of Associated Research Councils (Box 40)
    - Conference, Person-to-person. Contacts in International Relations (Box 40)
    - Confidential. Special File, [1972-1974] (Box 40)
    - Congressional Letter on Economy, 1972. Congressional Briefing on Needs of Private Institutions, 1973 (Box 40)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE) (Box 40)
    - Continuing Education (Box 40)
    - Copus Research Project (Box 40)
    - Corporate Chief Executive Officers, Conference of (Box 40)
    - Corporate Chief Executive Officers, Conference of. October 19, 1977 (Box 40)
    - Corporation for Public Broadcasting (Box 40)
    - Council for Policy Evaluation (Box 40)
    - Council of Southern Universities. Diuguid Fellowships, etc. (Box 40)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 40)
    - Council on Foundations, 1971 (Box 40)
    - Council on Foundations, 1972-1977, 5 folders (Box 41)
    - Council on International Relations and United Nations Affairs (Box 41)
    - Cpc Foundation (College Placement Council) (Box 41)
    - Cranks and other strange people (Box 41)
    - Cronkite, Walter, [1980] (Box 41)
    - Crotwell, Helen G. (Box 41)
    - Curricula Vitae (Box 41)
    - D. General correspondence, 1970-1985, 12 folders (Box 42)
    - Dalton, Harry L. (Box 42)
    - Daniels, Jonathan (Author, White House Witness, 1942-1945) (Box 42)
    - Dateline Duke (Box 42)
    - Davidson College (Box 42)
    - Davis, Walter. Nursing Program (Box 42)
    - Davison Club (Box 42)
    - Davison Professorships (Box 42)
    - Day Care Center (Box 42)
    - Dean of Arts and Sciences, 1979-1985 (Box 42)
    - Dean of Arts and Sciences. Undergraduate Faculty Council of Arts and Sciences (Box 42)
    - Deane, Disque D., [1975-84] (Box 42)
    - Deaths, 1973-1979 (Box 42)
    - Death Penalty (Box 43)
    - Deaths, 1980-1985, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Degrees, New [establishment of] (Box 43)
    - Degrees. Cases (Box 43)
    - Democratic Party, 1970-1982, 3 folders (Box 43)
    - Departments, 1972-1984. General Information (Box 43)
    - Departments. Anthropology (Box 43)
    - Departments. Art (Box 43)
    - Departments. Botany (Box 43)
    - Departments. Business Administration (Box 43)
    - Departments. Chemistry (Box 43)
    - Departments. Classical Studies (Box 43)
    - Departments. Computer Science, 1970-1984 (Box 43)
    - Departments. Computer Science. NSF Grant, 1980-1983 (Box 43)
    - Departments. Economics (Box 43)
    - Departments. Education (Box 43)
    - Departments. Education. Teacher Education at Duke University. Report, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Departments. Electrical Engineering (Box 43)
    - Departments. Electrical Engineering. Experiential Learning Laboratory. Selected Papers, 1975-1981 (Box 43)
    - Departments. English (Box 43)
    - Departments. Geology (Box 44)
    - Departments. Geology. African Project (Box 44)
    - Departments. German (Box 44)
    - Departments. History (Box 44)
    - Departments. Languages (Box 44)
    - Departments. Mathematics (Box 44)
    - Departments. Music (Box 44)
    - Departments. Physical Education, 4 folders (Box 44)
    - Departments. Physics (Box 44)
    - Departments. Political Science (Box 44)
    - Departments. Psychology (Box 44)
    - Departments. Public Policy Studies (Box 44)
    - Departments. Religion (Box 45)
    - Departments. Romance Languages (Box 45)
    - Departments. Slavic Languages and Literature (Box 45)
    - Departments. Sociology (Box 45)
    - Departments. Zoology (Box 45)
    - Development Office. - see also Institutional Advancement (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Administration, 1981-1983. Andy Parker (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Annual giving (Stachitas, Haltom, White, Ross) (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Bowles, John (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Corporate Relations (Jerry McBride, Mike Rierson) (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Dallas/Fort Worth Development Council (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Duke East/West Program, 1981-1983 (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Durham/Duke Campaign, 1983-1985 (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Foundation Relations. Barbara Smith (Box 45)
    - Development Office. GRAD System. William T. Harris (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Gift Records. Dorothy Brock (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Kirby, Rebekah (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Major Gifts. I. Croom Beatty IV (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Miscellaneous (Box 45)
    - Development Office. New York Development Council (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Plan of Action Report, 1982-1983 (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Planned Giving. Susan Marchase&Ralph McCaughan (Box 45)
    - Development Office. President's Associates, 4 folders (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Proposals, 1981-1985, 3 folders (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Prospects (Box 45)
    - Development Office. Prospects, 1981-1983 (Box 46)
    - Development Office. Prospects, 1984-1985 (Box 46)
    - Development Office. Prospects. Busch, August, III (Box 46)
    - Development Office. Prospects. Finch-Mobley Gift (Box 46)
    - Development Office. Prospects. Gertz, J. Barry, Gift (Box 46)
    - Development Office. Prospects. Ludwig, D.K. (Box 46)
    - Development Office. Prospects. Sullivan, R.E., Gift (Box 46)
    - Development Office. Prospects. Wallace, DeWitt, 1977 (Box 46)
    - Development Office. Scholarship Banquet, 1979 (Box 46)
    - Development Office. Special Programs. Duke Seminar, 1983 (Box 46)
    - Dining Halls, [1973-1983] (Box 46)
    - Distinguished Professors (Box 46)
    - Distinguished Visitors (Box 46)
    - Divinity School, 1970-, 3 folders (Box 46)
    - Divinity School. Task Force, 1974 (Box 46)
    - Dobbs School, [Raleigh, NC] (Box 46)
    - Donaldson, Lufkin, and Jenrette. Endowment Conference, [1972] (Box 46)
    - Dormitory, building of, 1981-1985 (Box 46)
    - Drug Science Foundation (Box 47)
    - Drugs, 1970-1971 (Box 47)
    - Duke Alma Mater (Box 47)
    - Duke Durham Fellows Seminar, 1984 (Box 47)
    - Duke Endowment. Campbell, Stewart F., 1974-1978 (Box 47)
    - Duke Endowment. Davis, Archie. (Trustee) (Box 47)
    - Duke Endowment. Day, John F., Treasurer. 1970-1985, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Duke Endowment. DeButts, John D. (Trustee) (Box 47)
    - Duke Endowment. Educational Beneficiaries (Box 47)
    - Duke Endowment. Educational Institutions, Committee on, 1975-1984 (Box 47)
    - Duke Endowment. Felts, James R., Jr. (Trustee) Executive director, Hospital and Child Care Sections (Box 47)
    - Duke Endowment. Henney, Richard B., (Executive Director), 1969-1978 (Box 47)
    - Duke Endowment. Law Suit, 1976-1977 (Box 47)
    - Duke Endowment. McCall, Billy G. (Deputy Executive Director and Secretary), 1969-1984 (Box 47)
    - Duke Endowment. Miscellaneous, [1970-1985] (Box 47)
    - Duke Endowment. Perkins, Thomas L. (Box 48)
    - Duke Endowment. Pickens, Marshall I. (Box 48)
    - Duke Endowment. Proposals to the Committee on Educational Institutions (Box 48)
    - Duke Endowment. Rural Church Program (Box 48)
    - Duke Endowment. Sailstead, Robert J. (Box 48)
    - Duke Endowment. Semans, Mary Duke Biddle Trent [elected chairman] (Box 48)
    - Duke Endowment. Tanglewood, [N.C.] Meeting, 1976 (Box 48)
    - Duke Endowment. Terry Sanford and Thomas Perkins Joint Statement, February, 1973 (Box 48)
    - Duke Endowment. Trustees of, 1961-[1981] (Box 48)
    - Duke Environmental Center (and Rural Observatory Program) [see also School of Engineering] (Box 48)
    - Duke Family. Doris Duke, [1960]-1985 (Box 48)
    - Duke Family. Durden Project (Box 48)
    - Duke Family. James B. Duke. Biography (Box 48)
    - Duke Family. James B. Duke. Portrait (Box 48)
    - Duke Family. Nanaline H. Duke Fund (Box 48)
    - Duke Family. Property in New York (Box 48)
    - Duke Fellows in Communication Program (Box 48)
    - Duke Forest (Box 48)
    - Duke Homestead (Box 48)
    - Duke Indenture (Box 48)
    - Duke, James B., Distinguished Professors (Box 48)
    - Duke. History of the University (Box 48)
    - Duke Management Club (Box 49)
    - Duke Managers' Book Club (Box 49)
    - Duke Players, [1970-1979] (Box 49)
    - Duke Post Office (Box 49)
    - Duke Seminar, 1970, 1976, 1983-1984 (Box 49)
    - Duke Translation Service, [1975-1977] (Box 49)
    - Duke University Black Alumni Connection (Box 49)
    - Duke University Cemetery (Box 49)
    - Duke University Computer Kamp (DUCK) (Box 49)
    - Duke University Credit Union (Box 49)
    - Duke University Drama Program (Box 49)
    - Duke University Editor, 1971 (Box 49)
    - Duke University Educational Perspectives and Vistas (Box 49)
    - Duke University Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration (Box 49)
    - Duke University Institute for Learning in Retirement (Box 49)
    - Duke University Letters, 1980-1985, 4 folders (Box 49)
    - Duke University Marine Laboratory, 1970-1985 (Box 49)
    - Duke University Marine Laboratory. Dedication, 1974 (Box 49)
    - Duke University Marine Laboratory. Duke/University of North Carolina Oceanographic Consortium (Box 49)
    - Duke University Marine Laboratory. Marine Biomedical Center (Box 49)
    - Duke University Marine Laboratory. Ship Eastward, 1971-[1979] (Box 49)
    - Duke University Medical and Technical Development (DUMAT Corp.). Jobsis Niros-scope; Bonaventura Biosponge (Box 49)
    - Duke University News Service (Box 49)
    - Duke. Sarah P. Duke Gardens (Box 49)
    - Duke University Oxford Summer Program (Box 50)
    - Duke University Press, 1971-1985 (Box 50)
    - Duke University Research Council (Box 50)
    - Duke University Research and Development (DURAD) Energy (Box 50)
    - Duke University Stores (Box 50)
    - Duke University Symposium, 1981-1982. Science, Technology, Ethics, and Policy. (Box 50)
    - Duke University Union, 1971-1980 (Box 50)
    - Duke University Union. Cable TV (Box 50)
    - Duke University Union. Presidential Candidate and (Box 50)
    - Journalist Forum, 1979-1980 (Box 50)
    - Duke University Union. Travel Agency Project, 1980-1983 (Box 50)
    - Duke University. Sanford chosen President of (Box 50)
    - Durham Arts Council (Box 50)
    - Durham City-County Charter Commission (Box 50)
    - Durham Community Foundation (Box 50)
    - Durham Morning Herald (Box 50)
    - Durham Progress Group, 1980, 1985 (Box 50)
    - Durham, City of (Box 50)
    - Durham, City of. Community Education (Box 50)
    - Durham Schools (Box 51)